Milton R. Konvitz Additional Papers /4085
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Cornell University Course Documents; Committee Documents (Box 38)
  - ILR 309 - American Ideals First Exam (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - ILR 309 - American Ideals Second Exam (Box 38, Folder 24)
  - ILR 309 - American Ideals Third Exam (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - ILR 309 - American Ideals Fourth Exam (Box 38, Folder 26)
  - ILR 308 - American Ideals General (Box 38, Folder 27)
  - ILR 308 - American Ideals First Exam (Box 38, Folder 28)
- Course Documents; Student Files (Box 39)
  - ILR 308 - American Ideals Second Exam (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - ILR 308 - American Ideals Third Exam (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - ILR 308 - American Ideals Fourth Exam (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - ILR 404 - Poverty and Social Policy (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - ILR 499 - Special Studies Projects (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - ILR 502 - Labor Law (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Admissions (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Admissions - Current (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Admissions (1972-73) (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Undergraduate (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Graduate Assistants (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Teaching Associate - ILR 308, 309 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Graduate Student - Sultan Khan, S.G.A. (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Graduate Students - Harris, Susan (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Graduate Student - Yemane, Araya (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Graduate Students - Law School - Special Committee (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - A - Former Students (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - B - Former Students (Box 39, Folder 18)
- Milton Konvitz Publications (articles, etc) (Box 40)
  - Milton R. Konvitz Publications - 1963 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Milton R. Konvitz Publications - 1964 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Milton R. Konvitz Publications -1965 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Reprints 1965 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Publications 1966 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Publications 1967 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - 1968 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - 1969 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Publications - M.R. Konvitz (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - US Supreme Court Transcripts (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - NJ Court of Errors and Appeals (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Law Reviews (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Saturday Review (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Encyclopedia Britannica (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous Publications (Box 40, Folder 15)
- General Correspondence; Publications; Files (Box 41)
  - SF/SM - General Correspondence (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - U - General Correspondence (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - V - General Correspondence (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - W - General Correspondence (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - X, Y, Z - General Correspondence (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - American Studies Review (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Alien and the Asiatic in American Law (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - ACLU 50th Anniversary (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - American Jewish Committee Paper (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - American Jewish Cong. Book (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - American Quarterly - D.W. Koster (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Barilan Lectures Nov. 1980 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Bill of Rights Readers - 5th Edition (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Dictionary of American History (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Dictionary of History of Ideas - Equity, Ethics, Loyalty (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Encyclopedia Britannica (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Encyclopedia Judaica (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Encyclopedia of Philosophy (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Encyclopedia of Social Sciences (Box 41, Folder 19)
- Publications; Correspondence; Arbitration Cases (Box 42)
  - Materials Ordered (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Blackwell's (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Bobbs-Merrill (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - University of Chicago Press (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Columbia University Press (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Doubleday & Co. (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Foundation Press (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Harcourt, Brace and World (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Harper & Row Publishers (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Harvard University Press (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Knopf, Alfred A. (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Ktav Publishing House (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - MacMillan Company (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Penguin Books, Inc. (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Prentice-Hall Inc. (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Random House, Inc. (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Schocken (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Scribner's Sons (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Cornell University Press - Misc. (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Book Reviews by M.R. Konvitz (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - New York Times Article (May 18, 1969) (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - Letter to the Editor - New York Times (October 19, 1969) (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - Saturday Review (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - World Publishing Co. (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - West Publishing Co. (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - Miscellaneous Publishers (Box 42, Folder 26)
  - Invitations (Box 42, Folder 27)
  - Arbitration Cases - American Arbitration Association (Box 42, Folder 28)
  - Rome Cable Corporation (1 of 3) (Box 42, Folder 29)
  - Rome Cable Corporation (2 of 3) (Box 42, Folder 30)
  - Rome Cable Corporation (3 of 3) (Box 42, Folder 31)
  - University of Rochester (Box 42, Folder 32)
  - Shepard Miles (Box 42, Folder 33)
- Cornell University Correspondence; Course Documents; Committee Documents (Box 43)
  - ILR 482 - Poverty and Social Policy Fall 1971-72 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - ILR 508 - Poverty and Social Policy Fall 1970-71 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - ILR 508 - Poverty and Social Policy Spring 1969 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Law School - Poverty and the Law Fall 1968 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Jurisprudence - Law School Fall 1966-67 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Law and Society - Law School Fall 1967-68 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - 300 - Labor Law and Legislation (Assignment Sheet) (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Law School Course: Law and Society (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Law 85: Law and Society (Fall 1960) (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - ILR 502: Labor Relations Law and Legislation (Assignment Sheets) (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - ILR 600: Labor Relations Law and Legislation (Assignment Sheets) (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Minutes: Committee on Academic Freedom and Tenure (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Academic Freedom (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Academic Freedom Part 2 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Committee on Academic Freedom and Tenure: Minutes (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Committee on Academic Freedom and Tenure: Duplicate Statements (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Committee on Academic Freedom and Tenure: By-Laws and Other Legislation of Cornell University (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Committee on Academic Freedom and Tenure: Statements From Other Universities and Associations, re: Tenure and Academic Freedom (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - ACLU (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - ILR 291 (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - CURW Bible (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Courses: ILR 290, 291 - Development of American Ideals (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - ILR 291 - Examinations (#5) (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - ILR 291 - American Ideals Reactions to Course (June 1959) (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - ILR 291 - Questionnaire (1951) (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - Course 290 - American Ideals Questionnaire (January 15, 1951) (Box 43, Folder 26)
  - Course Outlines (Box 43, Folder 27)
  - Grades (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - "Permission" to use Material for Courses (Box 43, Folder 29)
  - Course and Classroom Schedules (Box 43, Folder 30)
  - ILR 300 - Labor Relations Law and Litigation (Box 43, Folder 31)
- Arbitration Case Files; Merrill Trust (Box 44)
  - Navy Department - Portsmouth, NH (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Watervliet Arsenal (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - NY Psychiatric Center (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Montour Falls Shepard Niles (1983) (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Geneva (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Sayre, PA Arbitration (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - SUNY Binghamton Arbitration (Thomas Page) (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Arbitration - Rochester - Martinez (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Arbitration - Elmira (Edward Huffman) (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Arbitration - Brooklyn (St. Mary's Hospital) (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Arbitration Case - Elmira (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Johnson City, NY (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Arbitration - Cortland (Firefighters) (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Arbitration - Rome (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Arbitration - Elmira (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - PERB Arbitration Case (Rome) (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Arbitration - Binghamton (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Lackawanna, NY (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - ILR School (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - Binghamton City Employees (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - IAMAW, Local 586 (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - Arbitration Forms, etc. (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - Hilliand Co. (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - PERB (Box 44, Folder 24)
  - Israel Bonds (Box 44, Folder 25)
  - Israel - Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 44, Folder 26)
  - Merrill Trust - General Correspondence (Box 44, Folder 27)
  - Merrill Trust -1975 (Box 44, Folder 28)
  - Merrill Trust - 1974 (Box 44, Folder 29)
  - Merrill Trust -1973 (Box 44, Folder 30)
- Cornell University Correspondence (Box 45)
  - University Staff - Miscellaneous (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Black, Max (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Siegel, Benjamin (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Young Israel - Ithaca Chapter (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - University Library (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Vicious Circle (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - University and Due Process (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Cornell Chronicle 1974 (Box 45, Folder 8)
- Student Files (Box 46)
  - Cheek, Logan McKee (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - C - Former Students (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - D - Former Students (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - E - Former Students (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - F - Former Students (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - G - Former Students (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - H - Former Students (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - I - Former Students (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - J - Former Students (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - K - Former Students (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - L - Former Students (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - M - Former Students (Box 46, Folder 12)
- Subject Files (alpha) (Box 47)
  - Cornell (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Cuomo (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Darwinism (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Free Speech and Press (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Genocide (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Gun Control (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Homosexual (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Immigration Ethnicity (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Israel (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Israel (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Judaism (Jews) (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Jewish Education (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Jurisprudence (Law) (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Labor (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Libel (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Liberia (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Liberia Agreements (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Liberia (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Marxism (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - Privacy (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - Population (Box 47, Folder 22)
  - Poverty (Box 47, Folder 23)
  - Right to Die, Right to Life (Box 47, Folder 24)
  - Terrorism (Box 47, Folder 25)
  - Wars - International Law (Box 47, Folder 26)
  - Women (Box 47, Folder 27)
  - Workfare (Box 47, Folder 28)
  - Welfare (Box 47, Folder 29)
  - Yiddish (Box 47, Folder 30)
  - Zionism (Box 47, Folder 31)
  - Jewish Studies Committee (Box 47, Folder 32)
  - Shiloah (Box 47, Folder 33)
  - Enrollment Statistics (Box 47, Folder 34)
  - Columbia (Box 47, Folder 35)
  - Harvard (Box 47, Folder 36)
  - Yale (Box 47, Folder 37)
  - AJS (Box 47, Folder 38)
  - Other Colleges (Box 47, Folder 39)
  - Jewish Studies - General (Box 47, Folder 40)
  - Other Colleges (Box 47, Folder 41)
- Student Files; Subject Files (alpha) (Box 48)
  - N - Former Students (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - O - Former Students (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - P - Former Students (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - R - Former Students (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Schimmel, Harold - Former Student (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Sa-Sh - Former Students (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Si-Sz - Former Students (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - T - Former Students (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - U and V - Former Students (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - W - Former Students (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - X,Y,Z - Former Students (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Abortion (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Affirmative Action (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Africa (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - American Jewish Committee (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - ACLU (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - America (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - Anti-Semitism (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - Asylum (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - Ant-Defamation Lg. (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - Bi-Lingual (Box 48, Folder 21)
  - Blacks (Box 48, Folder 22)
  - Censorship (Box 48, Folder 23)
  - Civil Rights - General (Box 48, Folder 24)
  - Comparable Worth (Box 48, Folder 25)
  - Constitution (Box 48, Folder 26)
  - Constitutional Law (Box 48, Folder 27)
- General Correspondence (Box 49)
  - A - Correspondence (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Adams, John Luther (Professor) (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Agus, Jacob (Rabbi) (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Alexander, Yonah (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - American Association for Jewish Education (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - ACLU (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - American Professors for Peace in the Middle East (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Ba-Bk Correspondence (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Bl-Bz Correspondence (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Bar-Niv, Zvi (Judge, Israel) (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Janet Belcove (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Becker, Aaron (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Bina Brith (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Cardozo, Michael H. (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Greenville, Clark (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Cornell University (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - D Correspondence (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - Danelski (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - Dince, Robert R. (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - E General Correspondence (Box 49, Folder 20)
  - Edelman, Hyman (Box 49, Folder 21)
  - Eisenberg, Milton (Box 49, Folder 22)
  - F - General Correspondence (Box 49, Folder 23)
  - Finklestein (Box 49, Folder 24)
  - G - General Correspondence (Box 49, Folder 25)
  - Gaulkin, Edward (Box 49, Folder 26)
  - Gotesky, Rubin (Box 49, Folder 27)
  - Greenstein (Box 49, Folder 28)
  - Groat, William D. (Box 49, Folder 29)
  - H - General Correspondence (Box 49, Folder 30)
  - Hebrew University (Box 49, Folder 31)
  - Hertzberg, Arthur (Dr.) (Box 49, Folder 32)
- General Correspondence (Box 50)
  - Hill, Herbet (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - I - General Correspondence (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - J - General Correspondence (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Jung, Robbi (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Ka-Ke Correspondence (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Kallen, Horace (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Karp, Abraham J. (Rabbi) (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Katsh, Abraham - President, Dropsie College (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - La-Le Correspondence (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Lf-Lz Correspondence (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Liberian Codification Project (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - M - General Correspondence (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - P - General Correspondence (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - R - General Correspondence (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Rackman (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - Memorial Foundation for Jewish Culture (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - N - General Correspondence (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - O - General Correspondence (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - Pilch, Judah, Dr. (Box 50, Folder 20)
  - Rosenberg, J. Mitchell (Box 50, Folder 21)
  - Rosenfield, Harry (Box 50, Folder 22)
  - Rosenzweig, Margaret and Simon (Box 50, Folder 23)
  - Sa-Se - General Correspondence (Box 50, Folder 24)
- Publications Files; Subject Files (Box 51)
  - Libel (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Religious Liberty and Conscience (Viking Press) (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Hebrew Culture Foundation (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous (1 of 2) (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous (2 of 2) (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Abortion (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Academic Freedom (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Henry Adams (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Affirmative Action (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Aging (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - America and Holy Land (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - American Jews - Judaism (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - America (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - America (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Animals (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Association for Jewish Studies (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Blacks (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Bob Jones University (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Busing (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - Censorship (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - Constitution (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - CU Comm. On Jewish Studies (Box 51, Folder 20)
  - Cornell University (Box 51, Folder 21)
  - Cornell University (Box 51, Folder 22)
  - Creationism (Box 51, Folder 23)
  - Criminal Justice (Box 51, Folder 24)
  - Declaration of Independence (Box 51, Folder 25)
  - Deregulation (Box 51, Folder 26)
  - Election of Israel (Box 51, Folder 27)
  - Emerson (Box 51, Folder 28)
  - Emeritus Professors Association (Box 51, Folder 29)
  - ERA (Box 51, Folder 30)
  - GET - Jewish Divorce (Box 51, Folder 31)
  - Hebrew Culture Foundation (Box 51, Folder 32)
  - Hebrew Culture Foundation (Box 51, Folder 33)
- Publications Files (Box 52)
  - Expanding Liberties (Viking Press) (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Festschrift - Dr. E.A. Burtt (Samuel Lindley, editor) (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Festschrift - Frankfurter (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Festschrift - Sidney Hook (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - J. Stone Festschrift (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Jewish Social Studies (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Judaism and the American Idea (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Judaism and Human Rights (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Konefsky Memorial (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Law and Contemporary Problems - Privacy (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Law and Morals (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Myth and Scientific Mind (Burkill) (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - On the Nature of Value - Constitution and Civil Rights (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Philosophy Forum (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Recognition of Emerson - University of Michigan Press (Box 52, Folder 15)
- Subject Files (Box 53)
  - S.S. Hollister (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Holocaust (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Sidney Hook (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Immigration (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Israel (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Ithaca and Forest Home (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Ithaca (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Judaism and Human Rights (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Kallen Centenary (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Labor (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Law and Religion (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Law and Science (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Liberia (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Liberia (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Liberia (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Memorial Foundation (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Poverty (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - NEH (Box 53, Folder 19)
  - Privacy (Box 53, Folder 20)
  - Race (Box 53, Folder 21)
  - Reviews of MRK Books (Box 53, Folder 22)
  - Slavery (Box 53, Folder 23)
  - Supreme Court (Box 53, Folder 24)
  - Temple Bethel (Box 53, Folder 25)
  - Terrorism (Box 53, Folder 26)
  - Travel (Box 53, Folder 27)
  - Wars (Box 53, Folder 28)
  - Yiddish Cornell (Box 53, Folder 29)
  - Zionism (Box 53, Folder 30)
  - HM Kallen (Box 53, Folder 31)
  - National Council on Religion and Public Education (Box 53, Folder 32)
  - Seley Necrology (Box 53, Folder 33)
- Subject Files; Miscellaneous (Box 54)
  - Hillel Advisory Board (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Midstream Magazine (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Medicare - Old (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Social Security (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Books (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - UN Declaration - Religious Discrimination (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Jewish Studies (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Driving Books (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Worker's Participation in Management (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Judaism and Human Rights (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Norton (Box 54, Folder 11)
- Correspondence & Miscellaneous Publications (Box 55)
  - Cullen, Donald E. (Box 55, Folder 1)
- Subject File Material & Correspondence received 1 file folder 11/15/89 (Box 56)
  - Jewish Studies (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Liberian Studies (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - TV Project (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Jewish Studies (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Arbitration General (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Final Report of the ILR Faculty Internal Review Committee (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - The Crisis of Minority Faculty at Cornell (March 1987) (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Law and Civil Liberties (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Jewish Studies (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Israel Diaspora Institute (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - US Department of State (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - American Civil Liberties Union (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Law and Politics (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Judaism (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - University Publications of America (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - The Rutherford Institute (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - The Williamsburg Charter (Box 56, Folder 17)
  - American Academy for Arts and Sciences (Box 56, Folder 18)
  - ACLU and Jewish Publication Society (Box 56, Folder 19)
  - Lilenthal (Box 56, Folder 20)
  - Midstream (Box 56, Folder 21)
  - Introduction by Milton Konvitz (Box 56, Folder 22)
  - Introduction by Konvitz (Copy 2) (Box 56, Folder 23)
  - US Department of Justice Office of the Solicitor General (Box 56, Folder 24)
  - Law and Court Cases (Box 56, Folder 25)
  - Constitution and Moments of Silence in Public Schools (Box 56, Folder 26)
  - Science and Censorship (February 1987) (Box 56, Folder 27)
  - Jewish Studies (Box 56, Folder 28)
  - Jewish Studies Replies (Box 56, Folder 29)
  - Jewish Studies (Box 56, Folder 30)
  - Jewish Studies (Box 56, Folder 31)
  - Jewish Studies (Box 56, Folder 32)
  - Holy Spirit Association for Unification of World Christianity v. Tax Commission of the City of New York (Box 56, Folder 33)
- Subject File Material & Correspondence 1 file folder 11/15/89 (Box 57)
  - Baron Documentary Project (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Judaism (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - US District Court for the District of Columbia (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Racism and Zionism (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - American Civil Liberties Union (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - "The Apologetics of Suppression: The Regulation of Pornography as Act and Idea" - Steven Gey (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Midstream (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Lewis Feuer (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Memorandums: New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relation (July 8 and August 2, 1988) (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Legal Essays (3) (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - American Civil Liberties Union (1 of 2) (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - American Civil Liberties Union (2 of 2) (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Ithaca Jewish Welfare Fund (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Max Black (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Cornell University (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - American Jewish Congress (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - International (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - American Civil Liberties Union (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - Civil Rights (Box 57, Folder 19)
  - University of Wisconsin (Box 57, Folder 20)
  - Law and Religion (Box 57, Folder 21)
  - Judaism (Box 57, Folder 22)
  - Speluncean Explorers (Box 57, Folder 23)
  - Law and Social Action (Box 57, Folder 24)
  - Judaism (Box 57, Folder 25)
  - Rhodes, Frank "Evolution Theory" (Box 57, Folder 26)
  - Judaism (Box 57, Folder 27)
  - International and Civil Rights (Box 57, Folder 28)
  - US Law and the Constitution (Box 57, Folder 29)
  - Hebrew Culture Foundation (Box 57, Folder 30)
  - Journal of Labor and Religion (Box 57, Folder 31)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 57, Folder 32)
- Class Notes (bd. Booklets) lectures (Box 58)
  - Development of American Ideals Notes (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Development of American Ideals Notes (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Constitutional Liberties Notes (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Law and Society Notes (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Poverty Notes (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Poverty Notes (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Books (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Articles and Reviews (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Bibliography (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Development of American Ideal - Spring 1965-66 (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Development of American Ideals - Fall 1966-69 (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Development of American Ideals - Spring 1967 (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous Notebook (Box 58, Folder 13)